Javier Delgado N.





I am coursing technology management at ULACIT. This university has been important for my professional development for all my improve in leadership that I have acquired and the opportunities that they have given to me for trainings in areas of my career and being in conferences like EXPOTELECOM. Working in the student's government has made me a person who knows how to deal with different kinds of people, people who think different than me. I have got the ability to communicate, deal and negotiate with people to take forward work.



Work Experience

Full Stack Developer Konrad Group. January 2016 - Present

-Developing websites using Drupal, Angular, jQuery, Ionic, Node JS, Mongo DB, Git, Gulp and SASS.

Java Developer. (Innovation and Business Strategy Division) Instituto Costarricense de Electricidad (ICE). May 2015 – December 2015

-Develop their own web information system to manage different departments using Hibernate, Spring, JSF and Oracle SQL.

Student Tutor ULACIT. January 2014 - April 2014



Skills

Interpersonal Skills

Identified by my good communication, knowing how to listen people who have different points of view. This is very important to take decisions in the best way.

Languages

- -Spanish (native)
- -English (advanced)

English in Chester

England

-Chinese (Beginner)

Javier Delgado N.





Education

Management of Technological Resources Latin American University of Science and Technology (ULACIT) 2016-2017

Certified Developer Front End Specialist Acquia 2016

Software Engineering
Latin American University of Science and Technology (ULACIT)
2013 - 2016

-Basic knowledge in Arduino & Android.

Computer Operator Colegio Universitario Boston, 2009





Others

Student's Government GOES ULACIT. March 2014 - April 2016

- -President of the student's government,
- -Representative of System Engineering.
- -Organizing activities to improve our knowledge in our studies.

-Gamer Fest ULACIT.

As leader of the project, we carried this out in the best, coordinating with videogame players from different communities.

Member of Civic House Club ULACIT, January 2014 - July 2014

- -Working on volunteer programs since January 2014.
- -Helping people who are needing with the knowledge we are acquiring in our university.